Where is care needed?

SEARCH  Submit

* Home Care Info [ ] 

* Types of Care [ ] 

* Our Story [ ] 

* Contact [ ] 

SEARCH  Submit

    How Home Care Works
    -------------------
    
    Learn how "in-home care" can help your loved one and why families across the country have relied on Visiting Angels since 1998 to provide the best senior home care.

    Types of Care
    -------------
    
    Our comprehensive services, including companionship, personal care, and specialized services, are designed to keep seniors safe and happy in the comforts of home.

    Life Care Navigation

Where is In-Home Senior Care Needed? Find care for your loved one Where is care needed for your loved one?

Enter zip code where care is needed:

or

Select the state where care is needed:

State Alabama Alaska Arizona Arkansas California Colorado Connecticut Delaware District of Columbia Florida Georgia Hawaii Idaho Illinois Indiana Iowa Kansas Kentucky Louisiana Maine Maryland Massachusetts Michigan Minnesota Mississippi Missouri Montana Nebraska Nevada New Hampshire New Jersey New Mexico New York North Carolina North Dakota Ohio Oklahoma Oregon Pennsylvania Rhode Island South Carolina South Dakota Tennessee Texas Utah Vermont Virginia Washington West Virginia Wisconsin Wyoming

Data Protection Policy
======================

_Effective/Revised November 20, 2019_

Visiting Angels includes Our Franchisees and Master Franchisees. This data policy will explain how our organization uses the personal data we collect from you when you use our website.

### What data do we collect?

Our Company collects the following data:

* Personal identification information (Name, email address, phone number, etc.)
* Preference for begin of services
* “How did you hear about us”
* Zip where service is needed
* Services requested
* Relationship to loved one
* Gender
* Age
* Medical condition of loved one
* Living arrangement
* Consulting/advisory services
* Funding source
* Budget for out of pocket expenses
* Hours needed for support
* Loved one’s feelings

### How do we collect your data?

You directly provide Our Company with most of the data we collect. We collect data and process data when you:

* Register online or place a request for any of our products or services.
* Voluntarily complete a customer survey or provide feedback on any of our services.
* Use or view our website via your browser's cookies.
* Call and speak with our call center.

### How will we use your data?

Visiting Angels collects your data so that we can:

* Process your order, manage your account.
* Email you with offers on other products and services we think you might like.

### How do we store your data?

Visiting Angels securely stores your data at secure data center located in the states of Iowa and Virginia in the United States.

Visiting Angels will keep your data up to a period of 50 years. Once this time period has expired, we will delete your data.

### Marketing

You have the right at any time to stop Visiting Angels from contacting you for marketing purposes or giving your data to other franchisees of Visiting Angels.

### What are your data protection rights?

Visiting Angels would like to make sure you are fully aware of all of your data protection rights. Every user is entitled to the following:

* **The right to access** - You have the right to request Visiting Angels for copies of your personal data. We may charge you a small fee for this service.
* **The right to rectification** - You have the right to request that Visiting Angels correct any information you believe is inaccurate. You also have the right to request Visiting Angels to complete information you believe is incomplete.
* **The right to erasure** - You have the right to request that Visiting Angels erase your personal data, under certain conditions.
* **The right to restrict processing** - You have the right to request that Visiting Angels restrict the processing of your personal data, under certain conditions.
* **The right to object to processing** - You have the right to object to Visiting Angels’ processing of your personal data, under certain conditions.
* **The right to data portability** - You have the right to request that Visiting Angels transfer the data that we have collected to another organization, or directly to you, under certain conditions.

If you make a request, we have one month to respond to you. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us at

Email us at: contact@visitingangels.com

Call us:1-800-365-4189

Or write to us at: 937 Haverford Road Suite 200, Bryn Mawr PA 19010

### What are cookies?

Cookies are text files placed on your computer to collect standard Internet log information and visitor behavior information. When you visit our websites, we may collect information from you automatically through cookies or similar technology.

For further information, visit allaboutcookies.org.

### How do we use cookies?

Visiting Angels uses cookies in a range of ways to improve your experience on our website, including:

* Keeping you signed in
* Understanding how you use our website

### What types of cookies do we use?

There are several different types of cookies, however, our website uses:

* Functionality – Visiting Angels uses these cookies so that we recognize you on our website and remember your previously selected preferences. These could include what language you prefer and location you are in. A mix of first-party and third-party cookies are used.
* Advertising - Visiting Angels uses these cookies to collect information about your visit to our website, the content you viewed, the links you followed and information about your browser, device, and your IP address. Visiting Angels sometimes shares some limited aspects of this data with third parties for advertising purposes. We may also share online data collected through cookies with our advertising partners. This means that when you.
* Visit another website, you may be shown advertising based on your browsing patterns on our website.

### How to manage cookies

You can set your browser not to accept cookies, and the above website tells you how to remove cookies from your browser. However, in a few cases, some of our website features may not function as a result.

### Data Policies of other websites

The Visiting Angels website contains links to other websites. Our data policy applies only to our website, so if you click on a link to another website, you should read their policies.

### Changes to our Data Policy

Visiting Angels keeps its data policy under regular review and places any updates on this web page.

### Our Privacy Policy

To review Visiting Angels Privacy Policy, [click here](https://www.visitingangels.com/privacy-policy).

### How to contact us

If you have any questions about Visiting Angels’ data policy, the data we hold on you, or you would like to exercise one of your data protection rights, please do not hesitate to contact us.

Email us at: contact@visitingangels.com

Call us:1-800-365-4189

Or write to us at: 937 Haverford Road Suite 200, Bryn Mawr PA 19010

###   

\*Each Visiting Angels agency is a franchise that is independently owned and operated. The Franchisor, Living Assistance Services Inc., does not control or manage the day to day business operations of any Visiting Angels franchised agency.

#### Knowledge Center

 related  categories

[When the Elderly Need Help, Who is Their "Natural Caregiver?”](https://www.visitingangels.com/knowledge-center/care-options/when-the-elderly-need-help-who-is-their-natural-caregiver/406)

[“What Is Alzheimer’s?”: 3 Ways of Understanding Alzheimer’s Disease](https://www.visitingangels.com/knowledge-center/family-caregiver-support/what-is-alzheimers-3-ways-of-understanding-alzheimers-disease/347)

[Everything You Should Know About Adult Care (Non-Senior Home Care)](https://www.visitingangels.com/knowledge-center/care-options/everything-you-should-know-about-adult-care-non-senior-home-care/40)

[

](https://www.visitingangels.com/contact-us)

##### Subscribe to get the resources designed to help your loved one live at home.

Get Started Today

Contact a franchised Visiting Angels office in your area for information on elderly home care services.

Home Care Info

Types of Care

Resources

Our Story

Contact

Not all services are available at all locations. Please check with your [local agency](https://www.visitingangels.com/office-locator).

[Living Assistance Services, Inc. Copyright® 2024](https://www.visitingangels.com/home-care-franchise-opportunities "senior home care franchise opportunities") 937 Haverford Road Suite 200 Bryn Mawr PA 19010 [1-800-365-4189](tel: 1-800-365-4189 "1 800 number")

Each Visiting Angels agency is a franchise that is independently owned and operated. Release v.Release.ReleaseId  
The Franchisor, Living Assistance Services Inc., does not control or manage the day to day business operations of any Visiting Angels franchised agency.

»

Top 2024 Franchise Leader on  
[Franchise Business Review](https://vimeo.com/932936413).

[

Visiting Angels UK](https://www.visiting-angels.co.uk/)

[

Visiting Angels Korea](http://www.visitingangels.co.kr/)

[

Visiting Angels Mexico](http://www.visitingangels.com.mx/)

[

Senior Home Care By Angels Canada](http://www.seniorhomecarebyangels.com/)

Yes, please take me there. No, I am looking for services in a different state.
